Guide to the University of Chicago Office of the Vice-President Records 1937-1946
University of Chicago Library
- Football, "Is it Goodbye College Football?" Liberty, 21 September 1940 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Fortune, Telephone Silencer, 1938-1939 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Fortune, Raymond Leslie Buell, 1939-1940 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Fortune, Chamberlain, Joe Davenport, Russell (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Fortune, 1940-1941, Chamberlain, John Hodgins, Eric (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Fortune, 1941-1942 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Fortune, 1942-1943 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Fortune, 1943-1944 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Fosdick, Raymond, 1940-1941 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Foundations, 1938-1939 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- Freeman, Martin, 1938-1939 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- Freeman, Martin, 1939-1940 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- Freshman Week, 1939-1940 (Box 28, Folder 27)
- Friends of the Library, 1937-1938 (Box 28, Folder 28)
- Frodin, Reuben, 1939-1940 (Box 28, Folder 29)
- Frodin, Reuben, 1941-1942 (Box 28, Folder 30)
- Frodin, Reuben, 1942-1943 (Box 28, Folder 31)
- Frodin, Reuben, 1943-1944 (Box 28, Folder 32)
- Fuller, Buckminster, 1938-1939 (Box 28, Folder 33)
- G, general, 1937-1938, Gale, Henry Garrett, Paul Garrison, Lloyd Gear, Harry Geiling, E. M. K. Gerard, Ralph Gilson, Howard Glover, Charles H. Gortatowsky, J. D. (Box 28, Folder 34)
- G, general, 1937-1938, Greene, Jerome Greenleaf, Charles Griffith, Coleman Gross, David (Box 28, Folder 35)
- G, general, 1938-1939, Gale, Dean Henry Garrison, L. K. Geddes, C. S. Gee, Wilson George Williams College Gideonse, Harry D. Gilkey, C. W. Goodman, Paul Gottschalk, Louis (Box 28, Folder 36)
- G, general, 1939-1940, Gallup, George Garrett, Paul Gass, Carl Leo Gailing, E. M. K. Gideonse, Harry Giebish, John Gilkey, Charles E. Glaser, Dan Glick, Ira Glore, Charles F. Gonser, Thomas A. Goodspeed, C. T. B. Gordon, Charles U. Gordon, Harold J. Gorgas, Nellie (Box 28, Folder 37)
- G, general, 1939-1940, Greene, Mrs. Chester Greenleaf, Carl Grimshaw, N. A. Gulick, Luther (Box 28, Folder 38)
- G, general, 1940-1941, Gale, Sam Gallup, George Galvin, Paul Gammons, Earl Ganz, William J. Co. General Foods Corporation General Motors Gideonse, Harry D. Giersbach, W. C. Gilbert, John F. Gilkey, Charles W. Glore, Charles F. Goldblatt, Maurice Golze, Richard Goodman, Howard Goodman, William Goodspeed, Charles B. Gosnell, Harold F. Gottschalk, Louis (Box 29, Folder 1)
- G, general, 1940-1941, Graffis, Herb Graver, Grace Green, Dwight H. Green, Norman C. Greene, Arthur Gregory, Walter Guggenheim Foundation (Box 29, Folder 2)
- G, general, 1941-1942, Gager, John Gale, E. C. Galloway, G. B. Gallup, George Gardner, Albert Gardner, Martin Gardner, Robert Garfield, Harry A. Garrett, Paul Garrison, Lloyd K. General Amusement Corporation General Mills Georgia, University of Gerard, Ralph Gerling, John Gershman, I. Gibbs, John Gilkey, Dean Charles Goldbeck, Cecil Goldenstein, Robert Gonser, Thomas Goodspeed, Mrs. Charles (Box 29, Folder 3)
- G, general, 1941-1942, Graham, Frank P. Green, Governor Greenleaf, Charles Griswold, A. Whitney Griswold, Mrs. Denny Griswold, Glenn Grover, Allen Guck, Homer Gulick, Luther Gygi, Ota (Box 29, Folder 4)
- G, general, 1942-1943, Geiling, E. M. K. General Electric General Motors Gilbert, E. W. Goldthorpe, Mrs. Dorothy Goodman, Howard Goodspeed, Charles Gosnell, Harold F. (Box 29, Folder 5)
- G, general, 1942-1943, Graffis, Herb Green, Nelson L., Educational Screen Grove, W. A. (Box 29, Folder 6)
- G, general, 1943-1944, Gallup, George Geiling, E. M. K. Gilfillan Goodkind, M. Lewis Goodrich, Leland M. Gordon, Charles U. Goro, F. W. Gorrell, E. S. Gottschalk, Louis (Box 29, Folder 7)
- G, general, 1943-1944, Graffis, Herb Graves, L. M. Green, Dwight H. Gurian, Waldemar (Box 29, Folder 8)
- G, general, 1944-1945, Gause, John Gay, Mrs. Herbert Gelder, Madeline Gerard, Ralph Gettys, Cora Gilkey, Charles Gillette, Myra Gilmartin, Aron S. Gilson, Mary Goodrich, Carter Gordon, Charles Gordon, F. B. Gork, Mrs. L. Harry Gottschalk, Louis (Box 29, Folder 9)
- G, general, 1944-1945, Granger, L. B. Granik, Theodore Griswold, Gleb Guerard, Albert Gygi, Ota (Box 29, Folder 10)
- G, general, 1945-1946, Gilkey, Mrs. C. W. Glesenkamp, Mrs. W. L. Gottschalk, Louis Griessemer, Tom O. (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Garrett, Paul, 1940-1941 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Gates, Frederick T., 1937-1938 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Geiling, E. M. K., 1940-1941 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- General Education Board, 1937-1938 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- General Education Board, 1937-1938, Fosdick, Raymond Marshall, John Rockefeller, Laurance S. Rockefeller, Nelson Ruml, B. Stevens, David B. (Box 29, Folder 16)
- General Education Board, 1937-1938 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- General Education Board, 1938-1939, Harrison, W. K. Hutchins, R. M. Page, A. W. Rockefeller, N. A. Shumaker, E. E. (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Gideonse, H. D., 1937-1938 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Gifts to the University, 1937-1938 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- Gifts to the University, 1938-1939 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Gould, Bruce, 1937-1938 (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Gould, Bruce and Beatrice, 1938-1939 (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Great Men, tentative list to review, 1937-1938 (Box 29, Folder 24)
- Gustavson, Reuben, 1945-1946 (Box 29, Folder 25)
- Gygi, Ota, 1942-1943 (Box 29, Folder 26)
- Gygi, Ota, 1943-1944 (Box 29, Folder 27)
- H, general, 1937-1938, Hale, E. V. Hall, Arthur Hall, J. Parker Hamlin, Herbert Hanna, Phil S. Harper, Paul Harper, Samuel Harrell, W. B. Harrison, T. C. Harvard University Havill, Clara Hawthorn, Jessie L. Hayes, M. C. Hays, Will H. Hazelrigg, Hal (Box 30, Folder 1)
- He, general, 1937-1938, Hemens, Rollin D. Henley, W. B. Hetzel, W. C. (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Ho, general, 1937-1938, Hoefer, Harry Hoeppner, Hans Howard, Joseph Howe, Mrs. Lavinia Verrill Hoy, Charles Hu Shih, clipping from Honolulu Advertiser, 24 September 1937 Hyman, Sidney (Box 30, Folder 3)
- H, general, Hall, J. Parker Harris, Norman Waite, Foundation Harrison, Mrs. T. Carter Hayden, Charles, Foundation Hayes, St. John, Abramson & Shulman High, Stanley (Box 30, Folder 4)
- H, general, 1939-1940, Habas, Ralph A. Haley, Emilie Hall, Katharine Hamilton, William Handley, A. H. Hansen, A. H. Hanson, Charlotte P. Hard, William Harper's Magazine, Harper and Brothers Harper Memorial Library Harper, Paul V. Harris, Norman Waite, Institute Harrison, Margaret Havighurst, R. H. Hays, Will H. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- H, general, 1939-1940, Heidenheimer, Jack Hendrix College Hertzberg, Sidney High, Stanley Hitchcock, E. B. (Box 30, Folder 6)
- H, general, 1939-1940, Hogan, F. J., Herbert Hoover's attorney Hollister, Paul Holloway, Roland Hooper Hoover, Herbert Horn Hosmer, Sidney Houser, V. C. Howe, Edward Howe, N. D. Hulbert, James R. Humboldt Scholarship Husband, William L. Hutchinson, William Huth, Carl F. Hyde Park's Golden Jubilee Committee Hyman, Dick, King Features Syndicate (Box 30, Folder 7)
- H, general, 1940-1941, Halsey-Griffith Hamilton, H. L. Hamilton, W. J. Hanna, Phil Hanszen, Harry C. Harlow, Rex Harcourt-Brace Harper, Paul Harper and Brothers Harris Foundation Harris, Lina Small Harris, Sydney Harvard University Harvey, H. B. Haydon, Eustace (Box 30, Folder 8)
- H, general, 1940-1941, Heller, I. Henry, Nell C. Herald-American Hertzberg, Sidney, America First Hill, Roger Himmell, Richard Hinchley, Freeman (Box 30, Folder 9)
- H, general, 1940-1941, Hoban, Charles F. Hoeppner, Hans Hollister, Paul Hollowell, E. L. Hone, Basil Hopkins, Albert L. Horton, Horace Howard, Roy Howe, Edward T. Hubachek, F. B. Hull House Hunt, Lewis Hunt, Robert Hunt, Mutual Life Insurance Company Hunter, Robert Hutchins, Francis R. Hutton, A. J. Hyman, Sidney (Box 30, Folder 10)
- H, general, 1941-1942, Haas, Erwin Hackett, C. W. Hale, Gordon Haling, O. W. Hall, J. Parker Hallman, Frances Hanson, C. C. Hanz, Joseph E. Harbison, Frederick Harper, Paul Harper, Sam Harris, N. W. Foundation Harrison, R. W. Harshe, William Hart, Dan K. Harvard University Hatcher, C. Howard Haux, Junior R. Hawley, B. J. Haydon, Eustace Hazard, Paul (Box 30, Folder 11)
- H, general, 1941-1942, Heal, Edith Heller, Richard Henning, Arthur S. Hertzberg, Sidney Herzoff, Archie Hill, Isabel Hill, Lyn Himmel, Richard Hines, Herbert Hinkley, Arthur C. Hirschman, Duaine Hix, John (Box 30, Folder 12)
- H, general, 1941-1942, Hobbs, Dean Hoehler, Fred Hoeppner, Hans Holl, Julius Holland, Dudley Hoover, Herbert Hopkins, Albert Horton, Robert Houghton, Dale Houghton, H. H. Houston, University of Howard, Murray Howard, Roy Howe, Barbara Hudson, Howard Hufty, Page Hughes, Edward J. Hull, Denison Huse, H. R. Hutchins, Francis Hutchins, Mrs. Robert Hutchinson, R. A. Hutchinson, William Huth, Carl Hyde Park Herald Hyde Park Neighborhood Club (Box 30, Folder 13)
- H, general, 1942-1943, Hall, J. Parker Hanes, John Hanna, Phil Harcourt, Brace Harkins, William Harmon, H. G. Harshe, William R. Haygood, William C. (Box 30, Folder 14)
- H, general, 1942-1943, Heal, Edith Heald, Alan Heald, Henry T. Hemens, Rollin Hill, Emory K. (Box 30, Folder 15)
- H, general, 1942-1943, Holland, Dudley Hoover, Herbert Hough, Richard Houle, Cyril O. Howard, Martha Howe, Mrs. John P. Hu, Dr. Shih Hudson, Howard Hutchins, Francis Hutchins, Maude, Mrs. R. M. (Box 30, Folder 16)
- H, general, 1943-1944, Hadlock, Mrs. A. E. Hall, J. P. Hamel, Richard Hampson, Philip Hanighan, Frank Harmon, H. G. Harris, N. W., Foundation Harrison, Wallace K. Harshe, William R. Harvard Cooperative Society Haydon, Brownlee Haywood, Ralph Hecht, Frank A. Herald Tribune (Box 30, Folder 17)
- H, general, 1943-1944, Hemens, Rollin Henderson, A. D. High, Stanley (Box 30, Folder 18)
- H, general, 1943-1944, Holliman, B. S. Holloway, Barry Holman, Charles T. Hoover, Calvin Horst, George C. Howard, Roy Hoyt, Frank Hu, C. Y. Hu, Dr. Shih Hug, Hughes, Charles H. Hughes, Mrs. Everett Hughes, Rupert Hutchinson, William T. Hutton, Dorothy Hyman, Sidney (Box 30, Folder 19)
- H, general, 1944-1945, Harbison, F. H. Harrison, Paul Haydon, Brownlee Hazlitt, Henry (Box 30, Folder 20)
- H, general, 1944-1945, Heal, Edith Hennessy, Jossleyn Hershey, Louis B. Herzloff, Archie Hickenlooper, A. B. Hirschfeld, Gerhard (Box 30, Folder 21)
- H, general, 1944-1945, Hoban, Charles F. Hoffman, Paul G. Holland, Dudley Houle, Cyril Howard, Martha Huang, Robert Hudson, Howard Hudson, Robert Hughes, Mrs. Everett Hunter, M. H. Hutchins, Francis S. Hutchinson, Paul Hutchinson, William T. Huth, C. F. Hutton, Graham (Box 30, Folder 22)
- H, general, 1945-1946, Hall, Lawrence B. Harrell, William Harvey, Paul L. Hatcher, C. Howard Hatfield, Margaret Haydon, Brownlee Herrick, Virgil Hoselitz, Bert Hudson, Robert B. Hull House Association Huth, Carl F. (Box 30, Folder 23)
- Halifax Viscount, address at Commercial Club dinner, 8 May 1941, 1940-1941 (Box 30, Folder 24)
- "Harper, William Rainey", Milton Mayer, Alumni Magazine, June 1941, 1940-1941 (Box 30, Folder 25)
- Harrell, William B., 1938-1939 (Box 30, Folder 26)
- Harrell, William B., 1939-1940 (Box 30, Folder 27)
- Harrell, William B., 1940-1941 (Box 30, Folder 28)
- Harrell, William B., 1941-1942 (Box 30, Folder 29)
- Harrell, William B., 1942-1943 (Box 30, Folder 30)
- Harrell, William B., 1943-1944 (Box 30, Folder 31)
- Harrell, William B., 1944-1945 (Box 30, Folder 32)
- Haviland, Lilyan, 1940-1941 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Herald Tribune, 1937-1938 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- High, Stanley, 1937-1938 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- High, Stanley, 1938-1939 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- High, Stanley, 1940-1941 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- High, Stanley, 1942-1943 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Hoffman, Paul, 1937-1938 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Hoffman, Paul, 1939-1940 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Hoffman, Paul, 1940-1941 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Hoffman, Paul, Trustees' Talk, 8 January 1941, 1940-1941 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Hoffman, Paul, "The University of Chicago and the Democratic Way of Life", speech at University Club, 30 January 1941, 1940-1941 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Hoffman, Paul, 1941-1942 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Hoffman, Paul, 1942-1943 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Hoffman, Paul, 1943-1944 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Home for Destitute Crippled Children, 1939-1940 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- Hoselitz, Bert, 1944-1945 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Hough, Richard, Film Slide Proposal, 1941-1942 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Hough, Richard, Plan to make survey courses available, sound slide strips, 1942-1943 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Houlahan, Josephine, 1941-1942 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Howe, Edward T., 1941-1942 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Howe, John P., February-June, 1937-1938 (Box 31, Folder 21)
- Howe, John P., September 1937 to January 1938 (Box 31, Folder 22)
- Howe, John P., July- October, 1939-1940 (Box 31, Folder 23)
- Howe, John P., November-February, 1939-1940 (Box 31, Folder 24)
- Howe, John P., March-June, 1939-1940 (Box 31, Folder 25)
- Howe, John P., July-October, 1940-1941 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Howe, John P., November-January, 1940-1941 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Howe, John P., February-April, 1940-1941 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Howe, John P., May-June, 1940-1941 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Howe, John P., July-October, 1941-1942 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Howe, John P., November-December, 1941-1942 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Howe, John P., January-March, 1941-1942 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Howe, John P., April-June, 1941-1942 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Howe, John P., Selective Services, 1942-1943 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Howe, John P., July-October, 1942-1943 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Howe, John P., November-March, 1942-1943 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Howe, John P., March-June, 1942-1943 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Howe, John P., July-November, 1943-1944 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Howe, John P., December-June, 1943-1944 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Howe, John P., July-December, 1944-1945 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Howe, John P., January-June, 1944-1945 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Howe, John P., 1945-1946 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Hudson, Howard, 1937-1938 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Hudson, Howard, 1939-1940 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Hutchins, Robert M., February-June, 1937-1938 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Hutchins, Robert M., August-January, 1937-1938 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Hutchins, Robert M., "A Democratic Platform", 1937-1938 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Hutchins, Robert M., "What is a University?", 1937-1938 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Hutchins, Robert M., January-June, 1939-1940 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Hutchins, Robert M., July-December, 1939-1940 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Hutchins, Robert M., Gates Receipts and " Glory", 1939-1940 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Hutchins, Robert M., Convocation Address, 1939-1940 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Hutchins, Robert M., "Fate of Endowed Universities," Saturday Evening Post, November 1939, 1939-1940 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Hutchins, Robert M., "Future of the University", Trustees dinner to the Faculty, 10 January, 1939, 1939-1940 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Hutchins, Robert M., "Youth Speaks on Education for a Living", McCall's Magazine, October 1939, 1939-1940 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Hutchins, Robert M., "What Chicago Means", speech to alumni, 1939-1940 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Hutchins, Robert M., "What Good are Endowments?" Saturday Evening Post, 11 November 1939, 1939-1940 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Hutchins, Robert M., July-October, 1940-1941 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Hutchins, Robert M., November-January, 1940-1941 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Hutchins, Robert M., February-April, 1940-1941 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Hutchins, Robert M., May-June, 1940-1941 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Hutchins, Robert M., Memorandum concerning W. Benton's trip to Washington, November 1939, 1940-1941 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Hutchins, Robert M., "Challenge of the Marketplace", Rotary Club, 10 October 1940, 1940-1941 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Hutchins, Robert M., Commemorative Chapel Speech, "What the University Celebrates", 8 October 1940, 1940-1941 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Hutchins, Robert M., Convocation Address, 10 June 1941, 1940-1941 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Hutchins, Robert M., "Higher Education and the National Defense," Chicago Association of Commerce, 21 January 1941, 1940-1941 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Hutchins, Robert M., "I Worked my Way Through College", Liberty, 14 June 1941, 1940-1941 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Hutchins, Robert M., "Primer for Patriots", 1940-1941 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Hutchins, Robert M., Address to Trustees Dinner To Faculty, 8 January 1941, 1940-1941 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Hutchins, Robert M., "What Every Schoolgirl Ought to Know", draft, 1940-1941 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- Hutchins, Robert M., July-October, 1941-1942 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Hutchins, Robert M., November-December, 1941-1942 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Hutchins, Robert M., January-March, 1941-1942 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Hutchins, Robert M., April-June, 1941-1942 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Hutchins, Robert M., "Hutchins-Adler-Benton, U of C Triumvirate", Daily Maroon, 19 September 1941, 1941-1942 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Hutchins, Robert M., Convocation Address, "Relations of the University and Its Students to the War", 19 December 1941, 1941-1942 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Hutchins, Robert M., "University at War", Trustees Dinner to the Faculty, 7 January 1942, 1941-1942 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Hutchins, Robert M., Convocation Address, 19 June 1942, 1941-1942 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Hutchins, Robert M., July-October, 1942-1943 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Hutchins, Robert M., November-January, 1942-1943 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Hutchins, Robert M., February-April, 1942-1943 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Hutchins, Robert M., May-June, 1942-1943 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Hutchins, Robert M., Chapel Sermon, 4 April 1943, 1942-1943 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Hutchins, Robert M., "Education to Win the War", Rotarian, September 1942, 1942-1943 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Hutchins, Robert M., "Future of Endowed Institutions", "Schools Must Prove Right to be Supported", Rotarian, September 1942, 1942-1943 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- Hutchins, Robert M., "Theory of State", 1942-1943 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Hutchins, Robert M., July-November, 1943-1944 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Hutchins, Robert M., December-June, 1943-1944 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Hutchins, Robert M., Senate Controversy, May 1944, 1943-1944 (Box 35, Folder 19)
- Hutchins, Robert M., 1944-1945 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Hutchins, Robert M., Luncheon, New York, 19 April 1945, 1943-1944 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Hutchins, Robert M., 1945-1946 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Hutch Club, 1940-1941 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Hutch Club, 1941-1942 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Huth, Carl, 1940-1941 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Huth, Carl, 1942-1943 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Huth, Dean C. F., 1937-1938 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- I, general, 1937-1938, Ickes, H. L. Irwin, Miss (Box 36, Folder 9)
- I, general, 1938-1939, Illinois, University of, Press Illinois, University of, Public Information Iowa State Teachers College Irving, Clarence B. (Box 36, Folder 10)
- I, general, 1939-1940, Ickes, Harold Illinois, State of Illinois Commission Inglefield, C. C. Institute for Propaganda Analysts Instruction and Research, Committee on Interior, Department of Insurance, defamation Institute for Psychoanalysis Irwin, W. A. Isaacs, A. J. (Box 36, Folder 11)
- I, general, 1940-1941, Ickes, Harold Illinois League for Planned Parenthood Ingham, Travis Inlow, E. Burke Intercollegiate Broadcasting System Ivy, John (Box 36, Folder 12)
- I, general, 1941-1942, Ickes, Harold Information, Division of Ingham, Travis Institute of International Education International House Ireland, P. W. Ivey, Neal D. Ivy (Box 36, Folder 13)
- I, general, 1942-1943, Ickes, Harold Illinois Manufacturers' Association Institute of International Education Irwin, Watson (Box 36, Folder 14)
- I, general, 1943-1944, Imrie, N. W. Ireland, P. W. (Box 36, Folder 15)
- I, general, 1944-1945, Ingham, Travis Inlow, Burke Institute of Postwar Reconstruction (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Illinois Post-War Planning Commission, 1943-1944 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Illinois Post-War Planning Commission, Oscar Nelson, 1943-1944 (Box 36, Folder 18)
- International Chamber of Commerce, 1943-1944, Anderson, Alan Coates, W. H. Crowther, Geoffrey Dodd, John Guinness, Arthur Jones, Owen Lyttleton, Oliver Magowan, Lord Muirhead, J. W. Vansittart, Lord (Box 36, Folder 19)
- Institute of Military Studies, 1941-1942 (Box 36, Folder 20)
- Institute of Military Studies, 1942-1943 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- Invitations, luncheon, dinner, 1937-1938 (Box 36, Folder 22)
- Invitations, speaking, 1937-1938 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- Invitations, committee, 1938-1939 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Invitations, speaking, 1938-1939 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Invitations, writing, 1938-1939 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Invitations, speaking, 1941-1942 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Invitations, speaking, 1944-1945 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- J, general, 1937-1938, Jaeger, Werner Jampolis, R. W. Jenkins, Edward C. Jewett, F. B. Johnson, General Hugh S. Johnson, Norman Jones, John Price, Corporation Jones, R. L. Joshi, Sunder. L. Judd, Charles H. (Box 37, Folder 6)
- J, general, 1938-1939, Jewish Welfare Fund Johnson, Victor Johnston, M. E. Joshi, Sunder L. (Box 37, Folder 7)
- J, general, 1939-1940, Jackson, Emory B. Jessup, Walter A. Jones, Fred G. Jones, George Herbert Just, Henry F. (Box 37, Folder 8)
- J, general, 1940-1941, Jackson, Emory B. Jackson, Josephine Jacoby, Neil James, Sidney Jensen, John Jewell, Seth W. Johnson, Alvin Johnson, Daniel Johnson, Elliott Johnson, G. E. Johnson, Victor Johnston, John L. Jones, Edgar Jordan, Mrs. Edwin O. Judson, Clay Justitia, Sister Mary (Box 37, Folder 9)
- J, general, 1941-1942, James, George Jamison, John Joeckel, Carleton Johnsen, C. E. Johnson, Alvin Johnson, Elliott A. Jones, Gwethalyn Journals Judson (Box 37, Folder 10)
- J, general, 1942-1943, Jackson, Beth Jacobson, P. B. Jacoby, Mrs. Neil Jenkins, Victor Jennings, Dwight Johnson, Earl S. Johnson, John H. Johnson, Robert Johnson, Victor Johnson, Warren C. Johnston, Eric Jordan, Max (Box 37, Folder 11)
- J, general, 1943-1944, Jackson, Robert J. Jacob, Nina Jacob, Walter Jessup, P. C. Johnson, Robert Johnson, Walter Jones, Wellington Jordan, W. K. Journal of Commerce of New York Joyner, Sara (Box 37, Folder 12)
- J, general, 1944-1945, Jacob, Nina Jagger, Claude Jahnke, G. T. Jamieson, F. N. Jibby, D. K. Joeckel, C. B. Johnson, Walter Johnson, Warren C. Johnson, William G. Johnston, J. L. (Box 37, Folder 13)
- J, general, 1945-1946, Johnson, Joseph E. (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Jacoby, Neil H., 1941-1942 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Jacoby, Neil H., 1942-1943 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Jacoby, Neil H., Course for business executives on post-war adjustments, 1942-1943 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Jacoby, Neil H., Tuition certificates plan, 1942-1943 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Jacoby, Neil H., 1943-1944 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Jacoby, Neil H., 1944-1945 (Box 37, Folder 20)
- Jacoby, Neil H., 1945-1946 (Box 37, Folder 21)
- Jansky, C. M., 1944-1945 (Box 37, Folder 22)
- Jennings, Bill, 1943-1944 (Box 37, Folder 23)
- Jordan, W. K., 1941-1942 (Box 37, Folder 24)
- Jordan, W. K., 1942-1943 (Box 37, Folder 25)
- K, general, 1937-1938, Kahn, Louis Kay, Lambdin Keig, Marshall Kennan, J. C. Kent, Arthur Keppel, Frederick P. Kiplinger Washington Agency Kissack, R. A. Kleitman, Nathaniel Knowles, F. E. Kreines, Milton Kulka, Sig Kwapil, Genevieve (Box 38, Folder 1)
- K, general, 1938-1939, Kanaley, B. V. Katz, Wilber Keig, Marshall Kennedy, Walter S. Kinsler, David Kissack, R. A., Jr. Knight, Frank Knisely, Melvin Koch, Fred C. Kornhauser, Nathan Krogman, Wilton (Box 38, Folder 2)
- K, general, 1939-1940, Katz, W. G. Kellogg Foundation Kennedy, R. O. Klick, John J. Koons, B. D. Koos, Leonard Korns, Dick Kraus, E. J. Krueger, Maynard (Box 38, Folder 3)
- K, general, 1940-1941, Kellogg, John Kellogg, Paul Kellogg, W. K. Foundation Kennedy, Joseph Kennedy, M. A. Kenyon, Allan T. Keppel, Frederick P. Kersten, E. W. Kertesz, A. Kharasch, M. King Kingdon, Frank Kirschten, Ernest Knowlton, Hugh Kohler, Harry Korf, John Knox, Frank Koch, Dr. F. C. Kraft, James Kraus, E. J. Kreines, Milton Krogman, W. M. Kreuger, Maynard Krumbein, W. C. (Box 38, Folder 4)